Preliminary Guide to the North American Conference on British Studies records, 1949-2015 MS2187
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Original donations, 1949-2014; 1968-2007; Series 1; 25.5 Linear Feet
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee meeting, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - CBS Executive Committee meeting, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Cambridge University press, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Bibliographical series, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Registration forms, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - CBS general meeting minutes, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - CBS Executive Committee meeting, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Snow foundation prize, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Executive board meeting minutes, 1973-1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Executive board meeting, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: British Studies meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - British politics group, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Bibliographical series, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - CBS Executive Committee meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - CBS certificate of incorporation, by-laws, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Endowment Fund Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Delano, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - CBS member inquires, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Report: Endowmnent Fund Committee, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - NEH application, NACBS financial statement, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Conference materials, 1971-1978 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Appeal to past presidents, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: Ponko, biographical dictionary, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Intelligencer, 1972-1978 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: Albion, 1971-1978 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - AHA meeting, San Francisco, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - AHA affiliated societies, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - AHA program committee, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Studies in British history series, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: Epstein, Bacon, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence: Publications Committee, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Huntington fellowship, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Albion, annual report, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence: Albion subscription, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence: Albion, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Endowment pledges, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Snow foundation, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Floppy disks, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Expenditures, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Receipts, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Treasurer, 1982-1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Intelligencer, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Shearson Lehman Brothers materials, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Snow Prize, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - IRS/taxes, 1987-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Financial information, annual reports, 1977-1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Charter, by-laws, 1982-1987 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - IRS and tax-exempt status, 1986-1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Dues income, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Dissertation Fellowship Endowment Fund: gifts and pledges, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Tax returns, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, correspondence: Mike Moore, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Officers expenses, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Huntington Library Fellowship Award, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Savings account, checks, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Paper: chapter 1, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Paper: chapter 2, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Paper: chapter 3, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Paper: chapter 4, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Paper: chapter 5, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Paper: chapter 6, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Paper: chapter 7, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Paper: chapter 8, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, clippings: Longley, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1972-1982 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Albion and UCP: recipts, membership figures, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Dissertation Fellowship Endowment Fund: gifts and pledges, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: endowment, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: endowment, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Endowment, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Membership figures, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Shearson Lehman Brother account, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Contributions to regional CBS, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Dissertation prize, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Membership dues, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: British Council, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Dissertation fellowship, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Folger grant, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - By-laws, committee reports, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Sale of membership list, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - AHA San Francisco, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: ACLS, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Prize awards perspectives, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: prizes, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Boulder conference, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - AHA, Washington, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Member information, enquiries, 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Intelligencer, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Institute of Historical Research, 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Dues checkoff, 1988-1993 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Minutes, agendas, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: endowment, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Endowment fund, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Shearson Lehman accounts, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Income, expenses, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Diane Willen, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Bills, 1987-1991 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Personnel, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Job descriptions, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, annual report: Albion, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Minutes, Montreal, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Montreal conference, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Dues increase, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Endowment expenses and refunds, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Income for fiscal year, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Expenses for fiscal year, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Financial materials, 1983-1994 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - CBS, Midwest, 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - CBS, New England, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - CBS, Northwest annual meeting, Portland, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - AHA pamphlets, newsletter, 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - PCCBS, 1984-1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - SCBS, 1983-1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Student papers, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Reimbursement policy, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Job description: president, executive secretary, treasurer, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Membership Committee, 1986-1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Membership list, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Endowment Fund Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Endowment Fund Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Programs, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - CBS prize committee, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - CBS prize committee, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Council meeting agendas, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Council minutes, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Schwoerer files, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Houston council meeting, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, annual reports: Albion, 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Anglo-american conference, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Australian Vsitors Program, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - British Embassy, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - 1984 elections, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - 1985 elections, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - 1986 elections, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - 1987 elections, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: CBS meetings, 1959-1966 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Clippings, reports, memorandum and publications, 1958-1989 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: AHA, 1958-1966 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: AHA visiting scholars materials, 1953-1966 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: member information, interm reports, 1963-1989 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Memorandum on cooperation, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1961-1967 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1961-1962 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Jean Hecht, 1961-1966 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1961-1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1959-1966 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1964-1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Jean Hecht, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Jean Hecht, 1961-1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Jean Hecht, 1961-1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Jean Hecht, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Jean Hecht, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1959-1967 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - CBS, Public Record Office(PRO), 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: JBS, 1978-1983 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - CBS, research in progress, 1978-1980 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - CBS studies, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Snow trust application, 1980-1990 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Endowment, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: endowment, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Recipts, 1962-1967 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Cancelled checks, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Federal tax deposit coupon book, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Financial statements, 1985-1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Chinese-Brititsh council, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Membership records, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Membership records, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Membership records, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Membership records, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Dissertation endowment, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Shearson Lehman Hutton inc., 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Ordinary fund, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Snow endowment, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Irish Studies conference, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, memorandum: JBS editorship, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Haskins Society, 1982-1985 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, interviews: Archives, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities(NEH) Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Dissertation Fellowship Endowment Fund: records of deposits, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - British scholar immigrant controversy, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - JBS memorandum of agreement, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - JBS applications, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Lois Schwoerer, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Lois Schwoerer, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Tony Brundage, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Carolina symposium, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Financial materials, 1954-1961 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Development Committee, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Love Prize origins, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Conference group travel plans, members list, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - CBS history, 1966-1971 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Committee on placement, 1953 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Committee on documentary reproduction, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Chicago press, 1988-1991 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Finances, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - New York, costs, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - New Orleans, costs, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - New Orleans, correspondence, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Santa Carla, costs, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence: Bobb Webb, undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Paper: Man versus society in 18th century Britain, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Independent scholars, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Membership records, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence: AHA, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: JBS, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: JBS, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Endowment Fund, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Endowment Fund, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: English history, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 02/1965 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 03/1965 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 04/1965 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 05/1965 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 06/1965 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Meeting minutes, reports, 1952-1959 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Meeting minutes, reports, 1954-1964 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Meeting minutes, reports, 1959-1970 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Meeting minutes, 1977-1981 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Meeting minutes, 1982-1987 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Meeting minutes, reports, 1984-1990 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, Judith Hecht, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 03/1966 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 03/1966 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 04/1966 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 05/1966 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 06/1966 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Log book, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Arrangements with Asilomar, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Asilomar, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Publications, biography series, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - British Council prize winners, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Snow Prize, 1984-1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Love Prize citation, 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Love Prize, 1983-1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - AHA perspectives, prizes, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Rejected conference participants, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Program Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Program Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Program Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript: Changing Views on British History, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Dissertation Fellowship, 1986-1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Prize Committee, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Mid-Atlantic Conference on British Studies, 1982-1991 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - University of Colorado, Center for British Studies, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1957-1965 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1957-1965 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1962-1964 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence: Ruth Emery, 1962-1964 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Archives, 1980-1993 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Registration forms, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: John Clive, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: Peter Stansky, 1979-1983 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: membership, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: JBS, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: JBS, financial statements, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: elections, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: Nominating Committee, 1982-1990 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Conference drafts, reports, newsletters, 1972-1982 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence: Hugh Kearney, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence: Oxford Summer Conference, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence: British Council Book Prize, 1984-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Jean Hecht, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Price, Havran, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Intelligencer, Price, 1978-1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Vann, Meachum, Program Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Reba Soffer, CBS, 1978-1982 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Price, CBS meetings, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Price, CBS publications problems, 1978-1982 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Rocky Mountain conference, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence: Korr, 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence: By-laws committtee, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, miscellaneous materials: Vancouver meeting, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence: National Register of Archives project, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - CBS meeting, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence: Lacey B. Smith, 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: Finance Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Endowment Fund Commiittee, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1958-1965 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: Kruppa, Spurgeon, 1973-1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, clippings, 1975-1983 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, comments: Stansky, 1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Donovan, 1961-1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, clippings: Kross, Brunner, 1966-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, by-laws, clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Asilomar, 1983-1999 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: miscellaneous, 1976-1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Pacific Coast Conference on British Studies conference packet, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Pacific Coast Conference on British Studies membership data, 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Pacific Coast Conference on British Studies abstracts and submissions [1/2], 1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Pacific Coast Conference on British Studies abstracts and submissions [2/2], 1991 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Stansky report, 1999-2003 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Albion, 1976-1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Midwest and Pacific Coast Conference materials: pamphlets, programs, 1989-2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Midwest, Western, Northeast and Pacific Coast conference materials: pamphlets, programs, 1980-2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Pacific Coast Conference: pamphlets, programs, 1974-1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Mid-Atlantic, Southern Conference materials: pamphlets, programs, 1983-2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Pacific Coast, North East, Western Conference Annual meeting materials: programs, 2005-2007 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Pacific Coast Conference materials, 1974-1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Pacific Coast Conference materials, 1991-2004 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - NACBS book prize committee, 1976-1979; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - NACBS records, 1990-1992; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - NACBS records, 1994-1996; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - NACBS records, 1997-1998; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - NACBS records, 1999; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - NACBS records, 2000; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - NACBS records, 2001-2003; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - NACBS records, 1989-2014; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Gift of Dane Kennedy, October 19, 2014 (2014.036)
- Executive Secretary records, 2001-2004; Series 2; 64 digital object(s)
  Arrangement
  Arranged into three subseries by the donor. These include: annual reports, elections, and minutes and agendas.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains reports, correspondence, meeting minutes, meeting agendas, and ballots. The material dates from 2001-2004. All these records are electronic records stored off-line.
  Gift of Phil Harling, 4/26/2010 (2010.022).
  Existence and Location of Originals
  The digital objects in this series are stored off-line. Please see staff for assistance.
  - nacbs annual reports, 2002-2003; Series 2 Subseries 1; 44 digital object(s)
    These digital objects are stored off-line. Please see staff for assistance.
    This subseries contains reports produced by various groups within the NACBS.
    - 2002 reports, Series 2 Subseries 1; 9 digital object(s)
      - Albion Report 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 1
        This digital object is stored off-line. See staff for assistance.
      - BSI Report 02.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
        This digital object is stored off-line. Please see staff for assistance.
      - Essay Contest Report 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Exec Sec Report 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - JBS Report 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Program Chair Report 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 1
        This digital object is stored off-line. See staff for assistance..
      - Speakers' Program Report 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Treasurer's Report 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Webmaster Report 02.doc, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - 2003 reports, Series 2 Subseries 1; 10 digital object(s)
      - 2003.JBS.doc, Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Albion Editor's Report 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - BSI Report 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 1
      - Canadian Essay Report 03.doc, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 1